<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">CareerGuidance</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="match_career_button">Find your career match</string>
    <string name="career_options_button">See career options</string>
    <string name="careers">Careers</string>
    <string name="career_description">Description: \n
        A software engineer is responsible for the development, maintenance and operation of computer
        software to enable businesses and organisations to function as efficiently as possible. \n
        Software engineers work in a range of industries, from offices to manufacturing companies developing, operating and maintaining
        specific software to allow the company’s work to be carried out with as few disruptions as possible. Typically, a software
        engineer works with a business analyst or computer programmer to identify the needs of a company and to develop the
        specifications of the engineering project. Working with a small team of IT professionals, the software engineer completes
        the project following a particular development plan which covers each stage of the project, including testing, software analysis
        and the installation of completed IT systems.</string>
    <string name="career_salary">Average Salary: \n
        Recent graduates and newly qualified employees typically earn between £19,500 and £24,000 a year. With experience this can rise to
        between £25,000 and £38,000 depending on the size and nature of the company. Senior software engineers and those working in a
        more managerial role usually earn up to £45,000 a year.</string>
    <string name="skills_required">Skills Required: \n
        A software engineer is a highly skilled job and requires expert knowledge in computer programming and software development. More specifically the job requires: \n
        An excellent working knowledge of hardware, software and programming languages (e.g. Javascript)
        The ability to develop and interpret technical plans
        A creative approach to problem solving
        An excellent understanding of CASE (Computer Aided Software Engineering) tools
        Excellent communication skills, both written and verbal
        A good understanding of customer care
        Excellent interpersonal skills
        Good team working abilities
        The ability to explain complicated processes in non-technical language
        Good project management skills</string>

    <string name="universities_page_title">Famous Universities</string>
    <string name="university_name">Carnegie Mellon University</string>
    <string name="university_description">University Description: \n
        Carnegie Mellon University (Carnegie Mellon or CMU) is a private research university in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. \n
        The university began as the Carnegie Technical Schools founded by Andrew Carnegie in 1900. In 1912, the school became the
        Carnegie Institute of Technology and began granting four-year degrees. In 1967, the Carnegie Institute of Technology merged
        with the Mellon Institute of Industrial Research to form Carnegie Mellon University. The university\'s 140-acre (0.57 km2)
        main campus is 3 miles (4.8 km) from Downtown Pittsburgh and abuts the Carnegie Museums of Pittsburgh, the main branch of
        the Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh, Schenley Park, Phipps Conservatory and Botanical Gardens, and the campus of the University
        of Pittsburgh in the city\'s Oakland and Squirrel Hill neighborhoods, partially extending into Shadyside. </string>
    <string name="university_location">University Location: \n Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, United States</string>



    <string name="title_activity_main_tab_host">MainTabHost</string>
    <string name="title_activity_career_info">CareerInfoActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_university_info">UniversityInfoActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_university_list">UniversityListActivity</string>

</resources>
